Коісні Іто

Singapore

Research Interests

A PhD candidate at the National University of Singapore and consultant at the World Bank Group, interested in researching travel behavior, human perception, and equity with emerging spatial data sources, such as street-view imagery, and machine/deep learning techniques.

Education

The National University of Singapore

Aug 2022 - Present

PhD in Urban Analytics

Singapore

- Ongoing projects supervised by Dr. Filip Biljecki:
 - 1. Sequential and agent-based modeling of the effects of cycling interventions on intention to cycle

The National University of Singapore

Aug 2019 - May 2021

Master of Urban Planning

Singapore

• 4.53/5.00 cumulative GPA (Highest Distinction)

Soka University of America

Aug 2015 - May 2019

Bachelor of Arts, Liberal Arts with Concentration in Environmental Studies

Aliso Viejo, CA

• 3.95 /4.00 cumulative GPA (summa cum laude)

Council on International Educational Exchange

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017

Study Abroad Program

Dakar, Senegal

Honors

• Singapore International Graduate Award (SINGA) Scholarship	Aug 2022 – Present
• Japan Student Services Organization Scholarship (US\$40,000)	${ m Aug} 2020 - { m May} 2021$
• Soka University of America Makiguchi Scholarship (US\$10,000)	May 2019
• Soka University of America Dean's List (GPA is 3.7 or higher)	${ m Dec} 2015 - { m May} 2019$
• Soka University of America Merit Scholarship (US\$20,000)	${f Aug} \ {f 2015} - {f May} \ {f 2019}$

Publications

- 10. Ito, K., et al. (2024). ZenSVI: An Open-Source Software for Integrated Acquisition, Processing and Analysis of Street View Imagery. Manuscript under review.
- 9. Ito, K., Bansal, P., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Examining the causal impacts of the built environment on active transportation using time-series street view imagery. Transportation Research Part A: Policy and Practice, 190, 104286. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.tra.2024.104286
- 8. Ito, K., Quintana, M., Han, X., Zimmermann, R., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeability and walkability studies. International Journal of Geographical Information Science, . https://doi.org/10.1080/13658816.2024.2391969
- 7. Ito, K., Kang, Y., Zhang, Y., Zhang F., & Biljecki, F. (2024). Understanding Urban Perception with Visual Data: A Systematic Review. Cities, 152, 105169. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cities.2024.105169
- 6. Fujiwara, K., Ito, K., Ignatius, M., & Biljecki, F. (2024). A panorama-based technique to estimate sky view factor and solar irradiance considering transmittance of tree canopies. Building and Environment, 266, 112071. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.buildenv.2024.112071
- 5. Hou, Y., et al. (Ito, K.) (2024). Global Streetscapes A comprehensive dataset of millions of street-level images over 700 cities for urban science and analytics. ISPRS Journal of Photogrammetry and Remote Sensing, 215. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.isprsjprs.2024.06.023
- 4. Wang, S., et al. (Ito, K.) (2024). Mapping the landscape and roadmap of geospatial artificial intelligence (GeoAI) in quantitative human geography: An extensive systematic review. International Journal of Applied Earth Observations and Geoinformation, 128, 103734. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jag.2024.103734

- 3. Wang, Z., Ito, K., & Biljecki, F. (2023). Assessing the equity and evolution of urban visual perceptual quality with time series street view imagery. Cities, 145, 104704. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cities.2023.104704
- 2. Ito, K., & Biljecki, F. (2021). Assessing bikeability with street view imagery and computer vision. Transportation Research Part C: Emerging Technologies, 132, 103371. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.trc.2021.103371
- 1. Biljecki, F., & Ito, K. (2021). Street view imagery in urban analytics and GIS: A review. Landscape and Urban Planning, 215, 104217. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.landurbplan.2021.104217

Academic Services

Peer Reviews

Journal	Times Reviewed	Since
Cities	2	2024
ISPRS Journal of Photogrammetry and Remote Sensing	1	2024
Scientific Data	1	2024
Philosophical Transactions A	1	2024
Urban Informatics	2	2023
International Journal of Geographical Information Science	2	2023
Landscape and Urban Planning	4	2022
Computational Urban Science	1	2023
Journal of Geographical Systems	1	2022
International Journal of Applied Earth Observation and Geoinformation	1	2022
Environment and Planning B: Urban Analytics and City Science	2	2021

Services at Organizations

• International Forum on Urbanism (IFoU): Young Ambassador

2024 - Present

Talks and Poster Presentations

6. "Examining the causal impacts of the built environment on cycling activities using time-series street view imagery"

Jul 2024

Chaired a session and presented at the IATBR Conference

Vienna, Austria

5. "Advancing urban modeling with emerging geospatial datasets and AI technologies" Feb 2024
Gave an invited talk at the Global Space and Technology Convention 2024 Conference hosted by Singapore Land
Authority. Singapore

4. "Evaluating active mobility and urban perception with visual data"

Gave a guest lecture talk at a GIS course at the National University of Singapore.

Singapore

3. "Sidewalk the Talk: Translating street view imagery to correct perspectives to enhance bikeability and walkability studies"

Oct 2023

2. "Street View Imagery: Have we answered all the questions with it? What's left to do?" Sep 2023
Chaired a session at Spatial Data Science Symposium 2023.

Online

1. "Application of GIS in research and international institution."

Presented my research at Soka University of America, Advanced GIS Course.

Online

Work Experience

The World Bank Group — Poverty and Equity Global Practice

Presented a poster at the Urban Solutions and Sustainability R&D Congress.

Apr 2021 - Present

Consultant

Remote

Singapore

- Developed and maintained interactive data dashboards using Shiny and Golem frameworks to facilitate spatial data visualization and analysis.
- Implemented spatial lag models in R to analyze factors correlated with poverty and stunting.
- Led the collection, cleaning, and mapping of various spatial data sets to predict poverty rates in developing countries with XGBoost in Python.
- Conducted a capacity-building program for Tanzania's National Bureau of Statistics, imparting skills and knowledge on spatial analysis using R.

Johnson Controls

Data Analytics Intern

Singapore

 Constructed a data pipeline of PM2.5 data, weather data, and traffic data in Singapore on Azure Synapse for a real-time Power BI dashboard.

• Built a time-series model to predict PM 2.5 levels anywhere in Singapore with Python.

The World Bank Group — Tokyo Development Learning Center

Apr 2020 - Jan 2021

Nov 2020 - May 2021

 $Urban\ Development\ Research\ Intern$

Remote

- Compiled comprehensive data set of over 4,000 Tokyo-based startups' information, such as addresses, investors, and accelerators, using Python.
- Visualized financial performance of light rail transport system in Toyama prefecture between 2002 and 2019.

ENDA LEAD Afrique Francophone

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017

Research Intern

Dakar, Senegal

Authored a report on accessibility to potable water in 500 villages in the Saint-Louis region in Senegal.

Teaching Experience

CDE2212 AI for Design

Aug 2024 - Dec 2024

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

• Assisted in a comprehensive course on AI applications in design (generative models), providing in-person and online support during weekly lectures and tutorials, conducting lab sessions, and grading.

DEP5111 Planning Technologies

Jan 2024 – May 2024

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

• Assisted Master of Urban Planning students in mastering R Data Science through hands-on coding support, troubleshooting, and grading, enhancing their data analysis and visualization skills.

AR5805 Advanced Architecture Studio

Aug 2023 – Dec 2023

Teaching Assistant

The National University of Singapore, Department of Architecture

• Assisted the lead professor with logistical and administrative tasks, including the preparation of course documents and aiding in the smooth operation of lectures.

Supervising

• Shu Wang: Master of Applied GIS, the National University of Singapore

Apr 2024 – Jul 2024

• Heyang Hua: Master of Urban Planning, the National University of Singapore

Jan 2024 – May 2024

• Zeyu Wang: Master of Urban Planning, the National University of Singapore

Aug 2022 – May 2023

Technical Skills

Languages: Japanese (native), English (fluent), French (limited working proficiency)

Computer Skills: Python, R, SQL, Spark, ArcGIS, QGIS, Google Earth Engine, Azure, AWS, Power BI

References

• Filip Biljecki

Presidential Young

(Assistant) Professor

College of Design and
Engineering, The National
University of Singapore

• Prateek Bansal

Presidential Young

(Assistant) Professor

College of Design and
Engineering, The National
University of Singapore

• Zhang Ye

Associate Professor

School of Architecture,
Tsinghua University

• Takaaki Masaki Senior Economist The World Bank, Poverty & Equity Global Practice